[

](https://www.chatmeter.com/)[

](https://www.chatmeter.com/)

                * Chatmeter makes it easy for multi-location brands to be found, engage with customers, and optimize their revenues.
                    
                * Benefit from local and competitive brand insights using Chatmeter's AI-powered platform. It's more than Return on Investment - It's all about Return on Intelligence.
                    
                * Keep a pulse on the health of your business through real-time customer insights with Chatmeter's reputation management solution.
                    
                * Easily monitor, post and publish to multiple social media accounts from Chatmeter's all-in-one insights and operations dashboard.
                    
                * Attract and engage with potential customers across 140+ online directories with Chatmeter's listings optimization solution.
                    
                * Improve your SERP ranking and increase your online visibility while impressing your customers with the information they seek.
                    
                * Gain a 360° view of your customers’ wants, needs, and expectations with Chatmeter's survey solution.
                    
    * * [
            
            ](https://www.chatmeter.com/roi-of-brand-intelligence/)
        * [
            
            ](https://chatmeter.navattic.com/krs0s5e)
    * * [
            
            ](https://www.chatmeter.com/resource/blog/how-ai-technology-is-changing-reputation-management/)

[

](https://www.chatmeter.com/)

                * Chatmeter makes it easy for multi-location brands to be found, engage with customers, and optimize their revenues.
                    
                * Benefit from local and competitive brand insights using Chatmeter's AI-powered platform. It's more than Return on Investment - It's all about Return on Intelligence.
                    
                * Keep a pulse on the health of your business through real-time customer insights with Chatmeter's reputation management solution.
                    
                * Easily monitor, post and publish to multiple social media accounts from Chatmeter's all-in-one insights and operations dashboard.
                    
                * Attract and engage with potential customers across 140+ online directories with Chatmeter's listings optimization solution.
                    
                * Improve your SERP ranking and increase your online visibility while impressing your customers with the information they seek.
                    
                * Gain a 360° view of your customers’ wants, needs, and expectations with Chatmeter's survey solution.
                    
    * * [
            
            ](https://www.chatmeter.com/roi-of-brand-intelligence/)
        * [
            
            ](https://chatmeter.navattic.com/krs0s5e)
    * * [
            
            ](https://www.chatmeter.com/resource/blog/how-ai-technology-is-changing-reputation-management/)

Privacy Policy
==============

#### This privacy policy was revised February 2022

Chatmeter, Inc (and our affiliates) know that you care about how the information we receive from you is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. This Privacy Policy describes Chatmeter’s privacy practices in relation to information that we collect through websites operated by us from which you are accessing this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Domains”), through the software applications made available by us both online and mobile (the “Apps”), through our social media pages and apps located at:

(collectively, the “Social Media Pages”), and other services provided by us both online and offline; as well as through HTML-formatted email messages that we send to you that link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, including the Domains, the Apps and the Social Media Pages, the “Sites”). “You” or a “user” refers to any individual who visits or otherwise uses the Sites. By using the Sites, you are accepting and agreeing to the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.  
This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Chatmeter does not own or control, or to individuals that Chatmeter does not employ or manage.

This Privacy Policy also does not apply to information that we receive or handle on behalf of our customers in our role as a service provider, such as information that we receive through the Chatmeter Platform or other Chatmeter services, including any apps we make available for use by services subscribers (collectively, the “Services”). Such information is governed by the terms of the applicable services agreement, rather than this Privacy Policy.

### INFORMATION WE COLLECT

* Personal Information. “Personal Information” is information that identifies you as an individual or relates to an identifiable individual, including: name, title, company name, job function, expertise, postal address, telephone number, or email address. If you submit any Personal Information relating to other people to us or to our service providers in connection with the Sites, you represent that you have the authority to do so and to permit us to use the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
* IP Address: An IP Address may be identified and logged automatically in our server log files whenever you access the Sites, along with the time of the visit and the page(s) that you visited. Chatmeter uses IP Addresses to calculate usage levels of the Sites, help diagnose problems with its servers, administer the Sites, and monitoring the regions from which you navigate to Chatmeter Sites. Collecting IP Addresses is standard practice and is done automatically by many websites, applications and other services.

### HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION

* Other Information. “Other Information” is any information that does not reveal your specific identity or does not directly relate to an identifiable individual. This might include, for instance, browser and device information; App usage data; information collected through cookies, pixel tags, and other technologies; demographic information and other information provided by you; or aggregated information. We use this information to facilitate our operation of the Sites and for other purposes described below.

### HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION

Personal Information  
We and our service providers may collect Personal Information in a variety of ways, including:

* Through the Sites:  We may collect Personal Information through the Sites, e.g., when you request a demo, register for a webinar, contact us, subscribe to our email newsletter, download content (e.g. whitepapers), or register to use our Sites.
* Offline:  We may collect Personal Information from you offline, such as when you attend one of our events, during phone calls with sales representatives, or when you contact customer service.
* Through You: Chatmeter may collect information such as your location or your preferred means of communication when you voluntarily provide it. Note that there is no legal obligation for you to provide us with personal information and any information collected by us will be provided by you at your own will and with your consent. Unless combined with Personal Information, this information does not personally identify you or any other user of the Sites.

Other Information  
We and our service providers may collect Other Information in a variety of ways, including:

* Through Your Browser or Device:  Certain information is collected by most browsers or automatically through your device, such as your Media Access Control (MAC) address, computer type (Windows or Macintosh), screen resolution, operating system name and version, device manufacturer and model, language, Internet browser type and version, and the name and version of the Sites (such as the Apps) you are using.
* Through Cookies and Other Similar Technologies:  Cookies and other similar technologies may be used to collect Other Information. We may use third parties to serve advertisements on other websites that may be of interest to you, based on information collected about your use of our Sites and other websites.  To do so, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser (including through the use of pixel tags and web beacons).
* Through Your Use of the Apps:  When you download and use an App, we and our service providers may track and collect App usage data, such as the date and time the App on your device accesses our servers and what information and files have been downloaded to the App based on your device number.

Chatmeter also uses web analytics services, currently Google Analytics.

Google Analytics is a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses cookies and similar technologies to analyze how users use the Domains. The information generated about Domain usage (including your shortened IP address) is transmitted to Google in the U.S. This information is used to evaluate visitors’ use of the Domain, compile statistical reports on Domain activity, and provide other services related to the Site and Internet use. Google may also collect information about Domain visitors’ use of other websites. For more information about Google Analytics, or to opt out of Google Analytics, please go to: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

* By Aggregating Information:  Aggregated Personal Information does not personally identify you or any other user of the Sites (for example, we may aggregate Personal Information to calculate the percentage of our users who have a particular telephone area code).

### USE OF INFORMATION

Chatmeter May Use Information For The Following Activities:

* To respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests, such as to send you newsletters.
* To communicate with you and provide you with related customer service.
* To send administrative information to you, for example, information regarding the Sites and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies.
* To send you marketing communications, including via email and SMS in compliance with applicable laws, that we believe may be of interest to you.
* To personalize your experience on the Sites by presenting products and offers tailored to you.
* For our business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, fraud monitoring and prevention, developing new products, enhancing, improving or modifying our Sites and services, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns and operating and expanding our business activities.
* To allow you to participate in sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions and to administer these activities. Some of these activities have additional rules, which could contain additional information about how we use and disclose your Personal Information.
* As we believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; (d) to enforce our terms and conditions; (e) to protect our operations or those of any of our Affiliates; (f) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our Affiliates, you or others; and (g) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

### SHARING OF INFORMATION

Information about our users is an integral part of our business. We only share your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

* Third-Party Business Partners:  Chatmeter partners with a variety of businesses and works closely with them to market or sell products or services. In certain situations, these businesses operate within the Sites. We may disclose Personal Information to our partners for the purposes described above.  Some of our third-party business partners may co-sponsor events and other offerings with Chatmeter.  We may share Personal Information with these co-sponsors when you sign up for events or offerings to allow our partners to send you marketing communications and information that may be of interest to you, as permitted under applicable law.
* Chatmeter Blog and Social Media Pages: Personal Information may also be disclosed by you through the Sites, on message boards, chat, profile pages and blogs and other services to which you are able to post information and materials (including, without limitation, our Chatmeter Blog, at  [www.chatmeter.com/blog](https://www.chatmeter.com/blog) and the Social Media Pages). This information may appear in public ways, such as through search engines or other publicly available platforms, and may be “crawled” or searched by third parties. Please do not post any information that you do not want to reveal to the public at large.
* Agents and Service Providers: We contract with other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and may share your Personal Information with them to provide products or services to you, or to otherwise communicate with you, such as to provide marketing or offers on our behalf.  Examples may include removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, conducting billing, processing payments, engaging technical support for our services, providing customer service, and performing analysis related to our products or services. We may also provide your Personal Information to agents and service providers to verify or compile aggregate usage data that we provide to our partners. When we share this information in this way, we seek to require the agent or service provider to maintain the privacy, confidentiality and security of the Personal Information.
* Sweepstakes: We may share Personal Information with business partners or other third party sponsors of sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions.
* Business Transfers: In some cases, we may buy or sell assets or businesses. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Chatmeter may disclose Personal Information to a third party in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer, or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets, or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings).
* Protection of Chatmeter and Others: We may release Personal Information when we believe that release is necessary or appropriate (a) under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; (d) to enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements such as our Terms of Service; (e) to protect our operations or those of any of our Affiliates; (f) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain; and (g) to protect the rights, privacy, property, or safety of Chatmeter, our employees, our Affiliates, our users, or any other person or entity. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

### USE AND DISCLOSURE OF OTHER INFORMATION

We may use and disclose Other Information for any purpose, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable law. If we are required to treat Other Information as Personal Information under applicable law, then we may use it for all the purposes for which we use and disclose Personal Information.

In some instances, we may combine Other Information with Personal Information (such as combining your name with your geographical location). If we do, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information for as long as it is combined.

### HOW CHATMETER SECURES PERSONAL INFORMATION

We have implemented organizational, technical, and administrative measures to protect Personal Information within our organization, including security controls to prevent unauthorized access to our systems. While we take reasonable steps to secure your Personal Information from loss, misuse, interference and unauthorized access, modification and disclosure, you should be aware no security procedures or protocols are ever guaranteed to be 100 percent secure from intrusion or hacking, and there is therefore always some risk assumed by sharing Personal Information online. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of your account has been compromised), please immediately notify us.

### HOW YOU CAN CORRECT OR REMOVE INFORMATION

If you feel that any Personal Information about you that has been collected and stored by Chatmeter is incorrect, or if you would Personal Information about you removed from our systems, please notify us at info@chatmeter.com so that we may consider and respond to your request in accordance with applicable law. You may also request access to your Personal Information held by Chatmeter, by sending a written request to info@chatmeter.com.

For your protection, we may only implement requests with respect to the Personal Information associated with the particular email address that you use to send us your request, and we may need to verify your identity before implementing your request. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable, subject to applicable law.

Please note that we may need to retain certain information for record-keeping purposes and/or to complete any transactions that you began prior to requesting such change or deletion.

### RETENTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We will retain your Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

### CHOICES YOU HAVE

You can always opt not to disclose information. However, if you elect to do so, we may be limited in responding to your inquiry or providing services to you.

You may opt-out of receiving marketing messages from Chatmeter or our Affiliates by sending an email to [info@chatmeter.com](mailto:info@chatmeter.com) or by unsubscribing through the unsubscribe/email preference center link in an email.

You may limit the ability of Chatmeter and our affiliates to track your activities by using the Do Not Track functionality within your web browser.

### SENSITIVE INFORMATION

We ask that you not send us or disclose any sensitive Personal Information (e.g., social security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, biometrics or genetic characteristics, criminal background, or trade union membership) on or through the Sites or via other means.

### CAN CHILDREN USE CHATMETER’S SITES?

The Sites are not intended for minors under the age of 18. Chatmeter does not knowingly or specifically collect information about minors under the age of 18 and believes that children of any age should get their parents’ or legal guardians’ consent before providing any Personal Information. If you believe that we have mistakenly or unintentionally collected such information, please notify us info@chatmeter.com so that we may delete the information from our servers.

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Chatmeter may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. The “Effective Date” legend at the top of this page indicates when this Privacy Policy was last revised. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy on the Sites. Your use of the Sites following these changes means that you accept the revised Privacy Policy.

### QUESTIONS, CONCERNS OR COMPLAINTS

Your privacy is important to us. If you have any questions, concerns, or complaints regarding the way we collect and handle your information, please contact us by email at [info@chatmeter.com](mailto:info@chatmeter.com) or by mail at 225 Broadway, Suite 2200, San Diego, CA 92101  ATTN: General Counsel.

Chatmeter will take any privacy complaint seriously and any complaint will be assessed by an appropriate person with the aim of resolving any issue in a timely and efficient manner.

[

](https://www.chatmeter.com/)

Follow Us
